<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Honeyjar on Dropped Bits</title>
    <link>https://droppedbits.com/tags/honeyjar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Honeyjar on Dropped Bits</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 08:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://droppedbits.com/tags/honeyjar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Free non-trial for apps</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/02/free-non-trial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/02/free-non-trial/</guid>
      <description>On Friday, both Per and HoneyJar were made free for a limited time.
 We don&#39;t really need Per to tell us which option is the better deal.  Developers can&amp;rsquo;t offer free trials to their customers on the App Store, and customers aren&amp;rsquo;t always willing to commit dollars to new apps. That&amp;rsquo;s normal. Even though most apps cost less than a cup of coffee, at least a cup of coffee is something that people know and understand—everyone knows what a cup of coffee offers and can easily decide if it&amp;rsquo;s worth the price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now saving you even more money!</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/01/now-saving-you-even-more-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/01/now-saving-you-even-more-money/</guid>
      <description>How do you make two money-saving apps even better for your bottom line? Easy! Per and HoneyJar are both free for a limited time!
Download them now on the App Store and watch your savings add up even faster!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the App Store, developers can&#39;t hear you scream.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/16/developers-cant-hear-you-scream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/16/developers-cant-hear-you-scream/</guid>
      <description>A note if you&amp;rsquo;re leaving a review for any app on the App Store:
 Reviews are very helpful for letting the world know what you think of an app. Additionally, the more reviews an app gets, the higher it ranks when someone searches the App Store, which improves its visibility and &amp;ldquo;discoverability&amp;rdquo;. Developers of the app can&amp;rsquo;t reply to your reviews. So, if your review contains some kind of support request (&amp;ldquo;the app crashes when I do X&amp;rdquo;), the developer can&amp;rsquo;t get in touch with you to help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honeyjar v1.1 released</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/10/09/honeyjar-v11-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/10/09/honeyjar-v11-released/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve just released v1.1 of HoneyJar, a free update now available on the App Store.
This version adds support for iOS 8 and fixes a display bug on the iPhones 6, along with a smattering of other small bug fixes and performance enhancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, HoneyJar.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/09/04/hello-honeyjar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/09/04/hello-honeyjar/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to announce that HoneyJar, our first app for iPhone and iPod touch, has been released for sale.

You give every dollar you spend a job, whether you realize it or not.
In fact—if you want to take it to the extreme—you can argue that every dollar that isn&amp;rsquo;t working for you, is working against you. It&amp;rsquo;s keeping you from an early retirement. It&amp;rsquo;s keeping you from financial independence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>