<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dropped Bits</title>
    <link>https://droppedbits.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dropped Bits</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 07:57:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://droppedbits.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 07:57:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Our approach to privacy is pretty straightforward—we avoid collecting private information if we don&amp;rsquo;t have to, and if we do, we respect and protect it.
It&amp;rsquo;s important, however, to consider the difference between private and anonymous data.
Anonymous data Metrics We use Google Analytics and Squarespace Metrics to get an idea of how and why people visit this website. These services collect anonymous data to determine where website traffic is coming from, and where it goes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get in touch</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>Have a comment or question? Need support? Want to know more?
Just fill out the form below to send your message. I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to get back to you within one business day. And remember, your e-mail address will never be used for anything but answering your question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HoneyJar</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/apps/honeyjar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/apps/honeyjar/</guid>
      <description>HoneyJar is a future-value calculator inspired by one of Aesop&amp;rsquo;s fables:
 A jar of honey was upset and the sticky sweetness flowed out on the table. The sweet smell of the honey soon brought a large number of Flies buzzing around. They did not wait for an invitation. No, indeed; they settled right down, feet and all, to gorge themselves. The Flies were quickly smeared from head to foot with honey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Per</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/apps/per/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/apps/per/</guid>
      <description>Per helps you shop smarter by figuring out what gets you more for your money.
At its heart, Per is a price-per-unit calculator. Just give it the price and quantity for two options, tap the Compare button, and let Per figure out which one gives you the best deal.
Of course, you can do that kind of math with a basic calculator app. Per brings a few neat little tricks to the comparison-shopping party, though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free non-trial for apps</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/02/free-non-trial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/02/free-non-trial/</guid>
      <description>On Friday, both Per and HoneyJar were made free for a limited time.
 We don&#39;t really need Per to tell us which option is the better deal.  Developers can&amp;rsquo;t offer free trials to their customers on the App Store, and customers aren&amp;rsquo;t always willing to commit dollars to new apps. That&amp;rsquo;s normal. Even though most apps cost less than a cup of coffee, at least a cup of coffee is something that people know and understand—everyone knows what a cup of coffee offers and can easily decide if it&amp;rsquo;s worth the price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now saving you even more money!</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/01/now-saving-you-even-more-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/01/now-saving-you-even-more-money/</guid>
      <description>How do you make two money-saving apps even better for your bottom line? Easy! Per and HoneyJar are both free for a limited time!
Download them now on the App Store and watch your savings add up even faster!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Per v1.1 released</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/23/per-v11-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/23/per-v11-released/</guid>
      <description>A few little tweaks, enhancements, and bug fixes for you in this new version of Per:
See all the things Some view adjustments for iPhone 4s and iPhone 5/5c/5s users now put all the fields on screen, for more happy-tappy UI goodness.
Globalization, yo You can now choose the type of non-metric units used in your area (US vs. UK) from the Info page.
Nuke the site from orbit (it&amp;rsquo;s the only way to be sure) You can now clear the text from all the fields with one button tap, from the new Clear button (⊗) in the keyboard toolbar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the App Store, developers can&#39;t hear you scream.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/16/developers-cant-hear-you-scream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/16/developers-cant-hear-you-scream/</guid>
      <description>A note if you&amp;rsquo;re leaving a review for any app on the App Store:
 Reviews are very helpful for letting the world know what you think of an app. Additionally, the more reviews an app gets, the higher it ranks when someone searches the App Store, which improves its visibility and &amp;ldquo;discoverability&amp;rdquo;. Developers of the app can&amp;rsquo;t reply to your reviews. So, if your review contains some kind of support request (&amp;ldquo;the app crashes when I do X&amp;rdquo;), the developer can&amp;rsquo;t get in touch with you to help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, Per.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/09/hello-per/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/09/hello-per/</guid>
      <description>Pop quiz, hotshot: you&amp;rsquo;re in produce section at the supermarket, and you need carrots for tonight&amp;rsquo;s dinner.
Raw carrots are $1.09 per pound. Washed baby carrots are $1.99 for 907 grams.
What do you do?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
Per was created to answer exactly that question. It was inspired by my wife, who literally turned to me at the grocery store and said,
 &amp;ldquo;You should write an app that tells me which of these options is a better deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honeyjar v1.1 released</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/10/09/honeyjar-v11-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/10/09/honeyjar-v11-released/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve just released v1.1 of HoneyJar, a free update now available on the App Store.
This version adds support for iOS 8 and fixes a display bug on the iPhones 6, along with a smattering of other small bug fixes and performance enhancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, HoneyJar.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/09/04/hello-honeyjar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/09/04/hello-honeyjar/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to announce that HoneyJar, our first app for iPhone and iPod touch, has been released for sale.

You give every dollar you spend a job, whether you realize it or not.
In fact—if you want to take it to the extreme—you can argue that every dollar that isn&amp;rsquo;t working for you, is working against you. It&amp;rsquo;s keeping you from an early retirement. It&amp;rsquo;s keeping you from financial independence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/08/25/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/08/25/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to announce that—after what feels like an eternity—our first app for iPhone, HoneyJar, was submitted on Sunday for approval to the App Store team.
This marks a pretty big milestone, obviously. Dropped Bits incorporated almost three years ago, so it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time coming, too. And it&amp;rsquo;s been an interesting road so far, full of inspiration, hard decisions, learning, sacrifice, and happy little victories.
Turns out, going from idea to shipping your Minimum Viable Product isn&amp;rsquo;t as simple as you&amp;rsquo;d think—especially when your organization is having an identity crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>